Odzao Esther Lardze

Email | +233 543 920 766 Linkedin | Github Ghana, Kumasi

SUMMARY

I am a highly skilled Front End Developer with a experience in React Js, JavaScript, TailwindCSS, Next Js. I am keen to use my knowledge and practical experience to contribute to innovative projects and collaborate with diverse teams in creating exceptional web applications. As a quick learner, I embrace emerging technologies and constantly strive to seize opportunities that allow me to broaden my skill sets

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer (Contract)

Dec 2023 - Mar 2024

Remote – Ecentials-Web, Ghana

- * I developed an admin wallet dashboard designed for tracking users, withdrawals and deposits.
- * I worked on a sales report for users.

Junior Frontend Developer(Intern)

Sep 2023 – Dec 2023

Remote - Zap Technologies, Kumasi, Ghana

- * Designed and developed dynamic and responsive web application using next Js, Tailwindcss, firebase
- * Managed and directed a team to achieve project goals, ensuring timely completion and high-quality deliverables

EDUCATION

KWAME NKRUMAH UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

Ghana

Remote

BSc. Computer Science

2020 – 2024

HOLBERTON SCHOOLSoftware Engineering

Feb 2022 - April 2023

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages : JavaScript, Typescript

Frameworks: Next.js, React js, TailwindCSS

Dev Tools: Visual Studio Code, Git, Github

PROJECTS

Dev2Win <u>Live app</u> <u>Source Code</u>

· A pioneering platform revolutionizing student career development. Through project-based learning, personalized mentorship, and career guidance.

Youtube clone <u>Live app</u> <u>Source Code</u>

· A clone version of youtube. A user can watch videos, search for personalized videos, and read commets.

Tech <u>Live app</u> <u>Source Code</u>

 \cdot A UI solution built on the frontend for a client for future integration of backend

Geo Fosu Limited <u>Live app</u> <u>Source Code</u>

· A simple website built for a client to showcase their projects

PERSONAL TRAIT

Good interpersonal skills

Able to coordinate, lead and work in a team